http://www.daveandbusters.com/privacy-policy

Near You
Open Now!
With your existing account from
*By signing up you are opting in to receive Rewards emails to the email address provided
OOPS!
{{errors.signin.messages}}
OR
Sign in with a rewards account
Login
OOPS!
{{loginForm.errorMsg}}
Forgot Password
FORGOT PASSWORD?
OOPS!
{{forgotPassForm.errorMsg}}
Reset Password
RESET PASSWORD
OOPS!
{{resetPassForm.errorMsg}}
{{errors.reset.messages}}
All set!
Please check your email inbox to reset your password.
All set!
Create Account
Forgot Password?
Sign In
Card Balance Form
What's this?
Check Power Card Balance
OOPS!
Must complete recaptcha
You have {{cardBalanceChips}} CHIPS to use on games!
You have {{cardBalanceTickets}} TICKETS to use on prizes!
You have {{attractionChips}} ATTRACTION PLAYS to use on VR games!
You have {{rewardsPointBalance}} POINTS and are {{pointsToNextReward}} POINTS away from your next Reward!
Join Rewards and REGISTER your Power Card to receive points for every dollar you spend in store! SIGN-UP NOW!
Effective Date: January 1, 2020
We at Dave & Buster's, Inc., along with our affiliates, parents, subsidiaries and related companies (collectively, "Dave & Buster's"), respect your concerns about privacy. This Privacy Notice applies to personal information we collect on daveandbusters.com or other media form, media channel, mobile website, mobile application related, linked or otherwise connected to it or any guest Wi-Fi network in any of our stores around the world (collectively, the “Sites” or “Web Sites”) on which we have posted this Privacy Notice directly or by hyperlink.  This Privacy Notice describes the types of personal information we may collect on the Sites, how we may use the information, with whom we may share it and the choices available to you regarding our use of the information. We also describe the measures we take to safeguard the information and communicate how to contact us about our privacy practices.
Information We Collect
We may collect and/or obtain certain personal information (such as name and other contact details) through our Web Sites. The types of personal information we may collect include:• Contact information, such as your name, postal address, e-mail address, and telephone number• Names, postal addresses, e-mail addresses and telephone numbers of others to whom you ask us to send information• Username and password to sign-up for and access the Dave & Buster's Rewards program and your online profile• Payment information (such as payment card details, financial account information and billing address) • Birth date• Information about your education, work and military history, legal work eligibility status, and other information relevant to specific jobs for which you may apply• Other personal information you may provide to us• If you use our mobile applications, information, such as your device ID, your location and stores near you and visited by you, may be collected.In addition, when you visit our Web Sites, we may collect certain information by automated means, such as cookies and web beacons – geolocation information. The information we collect in this manner includes IP addresses, browser characteristics, device characteristics, operating system (e.g. Windows, Mac), language preferences, referring URLs, information on actions taken on our Site, and dates and times of Site visits. A "cookie" is a text file that web sites send to a visitor's computer or other Internet-connected device to uniquely identify the visitor's browser or to store information or settings in the browser. A "web beacon," also known as an Internet tag, pixel tag or clear GIF, links web pages to web servers and their cookies and may be used to transmit information collected through cookies back to a web server. Through these automated collection methods, we obtain "clickstream data," which is a log of content on which a visitor clicks while browsing a website. As the visitor clicks through the website, a record of the action may be collected and stored. We may link certain data elements we have collected through automated means, such as your browser information, with other information we have obtained about you to let us know, for example, whether you have opened an e-mail we sent to you. Your browser may tell you how to be notified when you receive certain types of cookies or how to restrict or disable certain types of cookies. Please note, however, that without cookies you may not be able to use all of the features of our Web Sites. If you use Site features operated by third-party social networking services (such as Facebook), we may receive information you have made available to those services, including the geographic location of your mobile device and other information about you (such as name, email address, gender, locale, time zone, languages, social media profile URL, personal website URL, biographical information, birthday, photo, list of devices, education history, work history, hometown, interests, current city, political views, favorite athlete and teams, relationship status and information, religion, name of significant other, and certain security settings information) and your contacts on those services. Some of these social networking services allow you to push content from our Web Sites to your contacts or to pull information about your contacts so you can connect with them on our Web Sites. Some of these services also will facilitate your registration for our Web Sites or enhance or personalize your experience on our Web Sites. You should make sure you understand the information your third-party social networking services may make available to our Web Sites. We may use and disclose the personal information we receive on our Web Sites through third-party social networking services as described in this Privacy Notice.
How We Use the Information We Obtain
We may use the information we obtain through the Web Sites to: • Create and manage your account;• Offer and provide products and services to you;• Communicate about, and administer your participation in, special events, programs, surveys, contests, sweepstakes, and other offers or promotions;• Send information to others;• Respond to and communicate with you about your requests, questions and comments;• Manage your application for employment with Dave & Buster's and contact you in connection with potential employment opportunities;• Process claims we receive in connection with our products and services;• Operate, evaluate and improve our business (including developing new products and services; managing our communications; determining the effectiveness of our sales, marketing and advertising; analyzing and enhancing our products, services and Web Sites; and performing accounting, auditing, billing, reconciliation and collection activities);• Perform data analyses and other processing (including market and consumer research, trend analysis, financial analysis, anonymization, encryption and tokenization of personal information);• Protect against, identify and prevent fraud and other criminal activity, claims and other liabilities; and• Comply with and enforce applicable legal requirements, relevant industry standards and our policies. In addition, we may use information collected online through cookies, local shared objects (also known as "Flash cookies"), web beacons and other automated means for purposes such as (i) customizing our users’ visits to our Web Sites, (ii) delivering content (including advertising) tailored to our users’ interests and the manner in which our users browse our Web Sites, (iii) marketing, (iv) demographic research and (v) managing our business. We may supplement data we collect through automated means with information about your location (such as your zip code) to provide you with content that may be of interest to you. We also use this information to help diagnose technical and service problems, administer our Web Sites, identify users of our Web Sites, and gather demographic information about our users. We use clickstream data to determine how much time users spend on web pages of our Web Sites, how users navigate through our Web Sites, and how we may tailor our Web Sites to better meet the needs of our users.To identify local shared objects on your computer and adjust your settings, visit here. We may use third-party web analytics services on our Web Sites, such as those of Google Analytics or Adobe Marketing Cloud. The analytics providers that administer these services use technologies such as cookies, web server logs and web beacons to help us analyze how visitors use the Web Sites. The information collected through these means (including IP address) is disclosed to these analytics providers, who use the information to evaluate use of the Web Sites. To learn more about Google Analytics and how to opt out, please visit here. To learn more about Adobe Marketing Cloud, please visit here. We may combine information we collect from you with information we receive from third parties and use it for the purposes described in this Privacy Notice. We also may use the information we obtain about you in other ways for which we provide specific notice at the time of collection.
Internet-Based Advertising
On the Web Sites, we may collect information about your online activities for use in providing you with advertising about products and services tailored to your individual interests. This section of our Privacy Notice provides details and explains how to exercise your choices. You may see certain ads on other web sites based on your visits to our Web Sites because we participate in advertising networks administered by third-party vendors. Ad networks allow us to target our messaging to users through demographic, interest-based and contextual means. These networks track your online activities over time by collecting information through automated means, including through the use of cookies, web server logs and web beacons. The networks use this information to show you advertisements that are tailored to your individual interests. The information our ad network vendors collect includes information about your visits to web sites that participate in the vendors' advertising networks, such as the pages or advertisements you view and the actions you take on the web sites. This data collection takes place both on the Web Sites and on third-party web sites that participate in the ad networks. This process also helps us track the effectiveness of our marketing efforts. To learn more about how to opt out of ad network interest-based advertising, click here.
Information We Share
We do not sell or otherwise share personal information about you, except as described in this Privacy Notice. When you post a comment on our Web Sites, third party social network services or blogs, we may publish your name and/or user ID thereon with your comment. We share personal information with third parties who perform services on our behalf based on our instructions. These third parties are not authorized by us to use or disclose the information except as necessary to perform services on our behalf or comply with legal requirements. We also may share the personal information we obtain with our affiliates, franchisees and joint marketing partners. We also may disclose information about you (i) if we are required to do so by law, regulation or legal process (such as a court order or subpoena), (ii) in response to requests by government agencies, such as law enforcement authorities, or (iii) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity. We reserve the right to transfer any information we have about you in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets (including in the event of a reorganization, dissolution or liquidation).
Your Options
We offer you certain choices about how we communicate with you and what information we collect from you. To update your preferences or ask us to remove your information from our newsletter e-mail lists please sign into to your Rewards account here or submit a request, please contact us as specified in the How To Contact Us section of this Privacy Notice.
Notice to California Residents
This notice supplements Dave & Buster’s privacy policy, applies only to California residents and is effective as of January 1, 2020. This California Privacy Notice sets forth the disclosures and rights for California consumers regarding their personal information, as required by the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”). Terms used in this California Privacy Notice have the same meanings given in the CCPA and the regulations of the Attorney General implementing the CCPA, unless otherwise defined.
This notice provides information about the categories of information that we collect from California residents generally, the sources of the information, the purposes for which we use the information, and the categories of third parties to whom we disclose the information for business purposes and to whom we sell Personal Information as defined by CCPA (and information on how to opt-out).
INFORMATION DAVE & BUSTER'S COLLECTS
Dave & Buster’s collects information that identifies, relates to, describes, references, is capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular consumer or device (”Personal Information”).
The following are the categories of Personal Information that we have collected from our users over the last 12 months (and examples of the types of information those include), the categories of sources from which that information was collected, the business or commercial purpose(s) for which the information was collected, the categories of third parties with whom we disclose the information for a business purpose, and the categories of third parties to whom this type of personal information is sold.
We may also collect and/or use additional types of information after providing notice to you before collection and obtaining your consent (to the extent such notice and consent is required by the CCPA).
View on desktop for full chart
Category of Personal Information Collected
Categories of Sources from which the Information was Collected
Business or Commercial Purpose(s) for which Information is Collected
Categories of Third Parties to whom this type of Personal Information is Disclosed for a Business Purpose
Categories of Third Parties to Whom this Type of Personal Information is Sold
Identifiers
We may collect this type of information from:
You,
Cookies and Tracking Technologies,
Third-party Service Providers,
Third-party social media companies,
Third-party business partners,
Third-party data resellers.
allow you to participate in features we offer or to provide related customer services, including our loyalty program and mobile application
recognize you across the Dave & Buster’s Sites and across devices,
tailor recommendations and offers we display to you,
process a Power Card purchase, or other transaction,
provide you with information, products, or services that you have requested or that we think may interest you,
investigate and prevent fraudulent transactions and other illegal activities or activities that violate our policies,
to comply with a legal obligation, such as respond to subpoenas or other legal processes,
process your registration, including verifying your information is active and valid,
contact you with regard to your use of any Dave & Buster’s Site or any Dave & Buster’s service and, in our discretion, changes to the Dave & Buster’s Terms of Use.
We may disclose this type of information to:
Service Providers, such as those who deliver our communications,
Third parties we partner with for contests, sweepstakes, or promotions,
Third-party advertising and analytics companies,
Other third parties (including government agencies) as required by law (such as pursuant to subpoenas or court orders).
Third-party advertising business partners may have access to this data, and this may be considered a sale under CCPA under certain circumstances.
Any categories of personal information described in subdivision (e) of Section 1798.80
We may collect this type of information from:
You
allow you to participate in features we offer or to provide related customer services,
recognize you across the Dave & Buster’s Sites and across devices,
tailor content recommendations and offers we display to you,
process a Power Card purchase, or other transaction,
provide you with information, products, or services that you have requested or that we think may interest you,
investigate and prevent fraudulent transactions and other illegal activities or activities that violate our policies,
process your registration, including verifying your information is active and valid,
contact you with regard to your use of any Dave & Buster’s Site or any Dave & Buster’s service and, in our discretion, changes to the Dave & Buster’s Terms of Use.
We may disclose this type of information to:
Service Providers, such as those who deliver our communications,
Third parties we partner with for contests, sweepstakes, or promotions,
Third-party advertising and analytics companies,
Other third parties (including government agencies) as required by law (such as pursuant to subpoenas or court orders).
Third-party advertising business partners may have access to this data, and this may be considered a sale under CCPA under certain circumstances.
Commercial information
We may collect this type of information from:
You,
Third-Party Service Providers,
Third-party social media companies,
Third-party business partners
allow you to participate in features we offer or to provide related customer services,
investigate and prevent fraudulent transactions and other illegal activities or activities that violate our policies,
process a Power Card purchase, or other transaction.
improve the Dave & Buster’s Sites or our services and for internal business purposes,
We may disclose this type of information to:
Service Providers who provide services on our behalf (including as needed to complete your transactions, to assist with our information technology and security programs, to assist with loss and fraud prevention, and to provide professional services to Dave & Buster’s),
third parties with whom we have joint marketing and similar arrangements,
other third parties (including government agencies) as required by law.
Internet or other electronic network activity information
We may collect this type of information from:
Cookies and Tracking Technologies,
Third Party Service Providers.
allow you to participate in features we offer or to provide related customer services,
recognize you across the Dave & Buster’s Sites and across devices,
tailor content recommendations and offers we display to you,
process a Power Card purchase, or other transaction,
investigate and prevent fraudulent transactions and other illegal activities or activities that violate our policies,
improve the Dave & Buster’s Sites or our services and for internal business purposes.
We may disclose this type of information to:
Service Providers who assist with our information technology and security programs, who assist with loss and fraud prevention, and who provide professional services to Dave & Buster’s
Other third parties (including government agencies) as required by law.
Third-party advertising business partners may have access to this data, and this may be considered a sale under CCPA under certain circumstances.
Geolocation data
We may collect this type of information from:
Cookies and Tracking Technologies,
Third Party Service Providers.
allow you to participate in features we offer or to provide related customer services,
tailor content recommendations and offers we display to you,
investigate and prevent fraudulent transactions and other illegal activities or activities that violate our policies,
improve the Dave & Buster’s Sites or our services and for internal business purposes.
We may disclose this type of information to:
Service Providers who assist with our information technology and security programs and who provide professional services to Dave & Buster’s
Other third parties (including government agencies) as required by law.
Third-party advertising business partners may have access to this data, and this may be considered a sale under CCPA under certain circumstances.
Inferences drawn from any of the information identified above to create a profile about a You
We may collect this type of information from:
You,
Cookies and Tracking Technologies,
Third-Party Service Providers
Third-party social media companies,
Third-party business partners,
Third-party data resellers.
allow you to participate in features we offer or to provide related customer services,
tailor content recommendations and offers we display to you,
improve the Dave & Buster’s Sites or our services and for internal business purposes.
We may disclose this type of information to:
Service Providers such as third party advertising and analytics companies, Other third parties (including government agencies) as required by law.
Third-party advertising business partners may have access to this data, and this may be considered a sale under CCPA under certain circumstances.
Exercising Your California Access, Deletion, And Do Not Sell Rights
You have the right to request that we disclose to you what Personal Information we collect, use, disclose, and sell, including the right to request that we provide to you the specific pieces of Personal Information we have collected about you in the prior 12 months (“Right to Know”) and you have the right to ask us to delete the Personal Information we collect about you (“Right to Delete”), subject to exceptions set forth in the CCPA. California residents also have the right to opt-out from the sale of their Personal Information. These rights are subject to some limitations, such as when we are retaining data to comply with our own legal obligations. You will not be required to create an account with us in order to submit a request. More information on each of these rights is below.
Response Timing
When you request access to the Personal Information we have collected or deletion of your Personal Information, we will typically provide the requested information within 45 days, and we will notify you within that time period if we need additional time to process your request. When you opt-out from the sale of your Personal Information, we will honor your request as soon as feasible, but no later than 45 days from the date we receive your request.
-Right To Know
1. Making A Request
To request the specific pieces of Personal Information we have collected about you in the prior 12 months, please complete this form: daveandbusters.com/contact, or email us at guest.relations@daveandbusters.com or call us toll-free at 1-888-300-1515.
We will provide the requested information free of charge up to two (2) times in a 12-month period, but please note that where we receive unfounded, excessive, or repetitive requests, we may elect to decline the request. Note also that we will not retain information we do not ordinarily retain in the course of our regular business practices.
2. Verifying Requests to Access
Please note that we will take steps to verify your identity in order to fulfill your request. We will first verify your email address is active and we will take steps to verify the information you provide to us.
In order to verify your identity, we will request that you provide: your name and email address/phone number (depending on what you have used to interact with Dave & Buster’s Sites).
In order to have us provide specific pieces of information, we will require a signed declaration under penalty of perjury that you are the consumer whose Personal Information is the subject of the request.
If we are unable to verify that the individual submitting the request is the same individual about whom we have collected information (or someone authorized by that individual to act on their behalf), we will not be able to provide the requested information.
-Right To Delete
The CCPA also provides a right to request that we delete personal information we have collected about you and for us to direct service providers to do the same, with certain exceptions as set forth in the CCPA. Note that you may also delete certain Personal Information you have provided to us through your online account.
When processing a request to delete, we may erase some information and we may de-identify some information (when we de-identify information, we implement technical safeguards and business processes that prohibit re-identification, business processes to prevent inadvertent release of de-identified information and will make no attempt to re-identify the information).
1. Making A Request
If you are a California resident and would like to request that we delete your information, please submit your request by completing the following form: daveandbusters.com/contact, or email us at guest.relations@daveandbusters.com or call us toll-free at 1-888-300-1515.
2. Verifying Requests to Delete
To ensure that we do not delete your personal information in response to a fraudulent request, once you submit the request, we will follow up to confirm that you want your information to be deleted.
In order to verify your identity, we will request that you provide: your name and email address/phone number (depending on what you have used to interact with Dave & Buster’s Sites).
If we are unable to verify that the individual submitting the request is the same individual about whom we have collected information (or someone authorized by that individual to act on their behalf) we will not delete the information.
-Right To Opt-Out Of The Sale Of Personal Information
The CCPA also provides a right to California residents to request to opt-out of the sale of Personal Information. Dave & Buster’s engages in online advertising practices that may potentially be considered “sales” under the CCPA.
If you are a California resident and would like to opt-out of the sale of Personal Information, please submit your request by completing the following form: daveandbusters.com/contact, or email us at guest.relations@daveandbusters.com or call us toll-free at 1-888-300-1515.
In addition, as we state in our privacy policy, some of the companies we work with for analytics and advertising purposes are members of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) or the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”) Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising and you may want to visit the following webpages, which provide “opt-out” mechanisms for participating companies: http://networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp and http://www.aboutads.info/choices/. You may opt-out from interest based advertising on your mobile device through your mobile device settings.
Users younger than 13
As noted in our Terms of Use for our Sites, Dave & Buster’s does not target users younger than age 13. and, therefore, does not knowingly collect or sell Personal Information of minors younger than 13 years of age.  With regard to users between the ages of 13 and 16, they must have the permission of, and be directly supervised by, their parent or guardian to use any of our Sites, and their parent or guardian must read and agree to our Terms of Use prior to use any of our Sites.
Right to Non-Discrimination for the Exercise of a Consumer’s Privacy Rights
California consumers have the right to not receive discriminatory treatment for exercising CCPA rights. We will not discriminate against you for exercising your CCPA rights.
Contact for More Information
You can contact us for more information by writing us at
Dave & Buster’s2481 Manana DriveDallas, Texas 75220Re: Privacy Policy – California Consumer Privacy ActEmail: guest.relations@daveandbusters.comToll-free phone: (888) 300-1515.
2. Other California Rights/Your California Privacy Rights
California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits residents of California to request certain details about how their personal information has been shared during the calendar year with third parties for those third-parties’ own direct marketing purposes, unless the business permits California residents to opt in to, or opt out of, this type of sharing. Dave & Buster’s qualifies for this alternative option. As noted above, we will not share personal information about you with third parties for their own direct marketing purposes if you do not opt-in, or if you choose to opt-out, at the time Dave & Buster’s offers you that choice.
If you are a California resident and you have questions about our practices with respect to sharing personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes and your ability to exercise choice, please write us at Attention Legal, at Dave & Buster’s, 2481 Manana Drive, Dallas, Texas 75220 or by email at: guest.relations@daveandbusters.com. You must put the statement “Your California Privacy Rights” in the subject field of your email or in the address line of your envelope. You must include your name, street address, city, state, and ZIP code. We are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, or do not have complete information.
Links to Other Web Sites
Our Web Sites may contain links to other web sites for your convenience and information. These web sites may be operated by companies not affiliated with Dave & Buster’s. Linked web sites may have their own privacy policies or notices, which we strongly suggest you review if you visit any linked web sites. We are not responsible for the content of any web sites that are not affiliated with Dave & Buster’s, any use of those web sites, or the privacy practices of those web sites.
How We Protect Personal Information
We maintain administrative, technical and physical safeguards designed to protect the personal information you provide against accidental, unlawful or unauthorized destruction, loss, alteration, access, disclosure or use.  Notwithstanding the aforementioned protections, Dave & Buster’s makes no representations, warranties or conditions or any kind, express or implied, with respect thereto.
Children's Privacy
Our Web Sites are not directed to children under the age of thirteen and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of thirteen on our Web Sites. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personal information from a visitor under the age of thirteen on our Web Sites, we will delete the information from our records.
Updates to Our Privacy Notice
This Privacy Notice may be updated periodically and without prior notice to you to reflect changes in our personal information practices. We will indicate at the top of the notice when it was most recently updated.
Your Acceptance of These Terms
By using the Web Sites, you agree to our Privacy Policy. We may also change the policy from time to time, so please be sure to visit this site often to see if anything has changed. If we post changes and you continue to use the site, you will be deemed to have agreed to the changes.
How To Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Notice, please contact Guest Relations by phone at 888-300-1515. You also may write to us at: Dave & Buster’s, Inc.Attention: Guest Relations2481 Manana DriveDallas, Texas  75220
